By going on that
fun class trip together...
Tani-kun!
...has brought us closer
than ever before!
Morning!
Have you recovered
from post-trip exhaustion?
Yeah.
And you, Suzuki-san?
Or that's how it could've been, but no.
Huh? What is it? What's wrong?
"Suzuki-san."
Oh...
Miyu.
But, Suzuki-san, you called me
by my last name just now, didn't you?
Really? Did I?
Well, we are at school,
so, you know, it's a little...
Yeah, it is.
If it were just the two of us,
well, then of course...
Of course, Tani-kun, you'd
certainly be more... you know? Right?
Please don't set the bar too high.
Even if there weren't any leaps
in growth or sudden developments...
I do feel that there were
small, positive changes.
What's come over you?
I am creating a summary of the historical
artifacts of cultural significance.
Japanese wabi-sabi.
Sato, your handwriting is so pretty.
Right?
Why are you the one acting proud?
That's so true!
I might just be imagining it, but...
I feel like Azuma's putting off
less negative aura than before.
HEH HEH HEH...
AFTER SCHOOL
Tani, did you already order
your class trip photos?
Not yet.
Tani, have you looked at the photos?
Tani-kun's social circle has expanded
a little without my noticing it.
No, not yet.
You should.
You should order this one and
this one. You look great in them!
THEY WERE IN THE BIG ROOM WITH HIM
I know you don't really think that.
I'm not buying them.
STARE
Suzuki is staring for some reason.
I want to see Tani-kun
looking good in a photo.
What kind of photo is this?!
It's the one we had the camera guy
take in the big room.
That's the alternate version.
You're all idiots!
Tani-kun, if you're not buying these,
then I will.
You don't have to buy them.
Which other ones should I buy?
If you order too many,
it can cost quite a lot.
That's right. After our
middle school class trip,
Gapacho ordered photos of just scenery,
which caused some
parent-related trouble.
Photos of just scenery?
Gapacho sure has refined taste.
I totally get it.
HE DOESN'T WANT PHOTOS OF HIMSELF.
HE WANTS A RECORD OF THE TRIP.
Well, I'm not in many photos,
so I guess this'll do.
Huh? There's a lot of you.
See?
ORDER
Ignore those! You get it, don't you?
There won't be any student council
work for a while, so I can relax.
Ever since they made me class rep while
I was out sick, I've disliked my class,
but when all's said and done,
the trip was fun!
I'm glad.
So... where are you going on your outing?
What?!
Oh, um...
YOU AND I ARE POLAR OPPOSITES
What do I do?
Want to go hang out somewhere?
Just the two of us.
It's not like me at all,
but should I do it anyway?
Dress fashionably...
A long time ago, Mom said...
SMILE
Oh, what's this?
Why are you all dressed up?
And ever since then,
I've felt vaguely embarrassed.
Is it weird?
I've hardly ever worn this dress.
Should I wear it now?
Will it be okay?
Is it weird for me to wear this?
I focus on how easy
things are to wear, so I don't know.
EX: ON THE CLASS TRIP
LOUNGEWEAR
BASICALLY THE SAME
Wearing what you want is the best!
YAY!
If people put you into random genres or
say other clothes look better, who cares?
GRIT...
Okay.
HON-CHAN IS ALWAYS
IN MY HEART...
Since I have the chance...
BOUGHT WHAT SEEMED PRETTY AT THE TIME, SO THEY'RE ALL DIFFERENT STYLES
I'll wear some of the accessories
I bought without a plan for using them.
Huh?
What's this?
What do I do?
My heart's racing and it just won't stop!
I'm going now.
What? You're leaving already?
Okay.
ALL DECKED OUT
I managed to leave
without my family seeing me!
WHEW...
It's only when I thought of
wearing this to go out
that I first realized I don't have
a jacket or shoes to match these clothes.
COAT BOUGHT TO WEAR
WITH SCHOOL UNIFORM
SNEAKERS BOUGHT
TO WEAR FOR P.E. (OUTSIDE)
I bought them because
I thought each one was cute,
so I didn't think about how they'd
coordinate with what I already had.
THEY SHOULD BE MORE LIKE...
Somehow...
THE STATION WHERE THEY'RE MEETING
I never really noticed before...
SHOWY
but all the girls walking down the street
look so fashionable!
SHOWY
QUICK
I will take these off after all!
GOOD NIGHT
I'm here!
Where are you right now?
Um... I'm here, too.
I'm at the top of the back escalator
on the platform.
I'm here too
GOOD NIGHT
I'm here!
Where are you right now?
Nishi-san
Incoming call
Hello? Nishi-san?
What's wrong? Did you get lost?
Oh. I'm already here.
What? For real?
Um, at the top of the escalators,
there's a... you might call it a plaza?
She's never gonna look at me.
I'm standing beside the ticket gates.
I'm here.
What? The reception isn't very—
Oh! I'm so sorry.
Why are you being so formal?
And why'd you scream?
I thought I'd bumped
into someone I didn't know.
But you were speaking
politely before that, too.
Are you nervous?
Are you really asking that?
Yes.
You mean "yeah."
Wait. Now that I think about it...
is Yamada-kun's hair
a little different than usual?
He put a lot of work into it!
No, hang on.
What does it usually look like?
Now that I think about it, I don't
usually look him in the eye when we talk.
SHE LOOKS AT THIS AREA
CHINATOWN
Going to a place I've never been before...
wearing something other
than my uniform...
walking together, just us two.
He feels even more like someone
from a different world than me.
Is it weird that I'm the one
walking next to him?
You hungry?
I am feeling peck— ry. Hungry!
If you're feeling peckry,
let's grab something.
I was going to say "peckish"
and changed midway.
I totally understand-ry.
Oh! That looks yummy!
Hey, I know it's kinda late to ask,
but is it okay that
we went where I wanted?
Yeah.
For some reason, I was really
craving a good meat bun.
Well, it has gotten colder.
Yeah, exactly.
AWARD WINNING
XIAO
LONG
BAO
ULTIMATE
I mean, I'm always eating steamed stuff
from the convenience store,
but the other day, on my way home,
one of the houses smelled like meat buns...
And that's when I thought,
"Oh, yeah! Chinatown!"
The convenience store I usually
go to is where Taira works.
Taira-kun. The boy with brown hair.
And then Mini had
Morimo dying of laughter!
Through Yamada-kun, I'm learning
more and more people's names.
And then, when I told Gapacho about it...
Wait. I was the only one talking. Sorry.
What?
"Steamed stuff"
from the convenience store.
What?
It's just, I was wondering why you
called the meat buns "steamed stuff."
Well, there's pizza buns
and stuff, too, right?
NIKUMAN
PIZZA BUNS
STEAMED
STUFF
YAMADA'S
PERSONAL RULES
I see.
STARE...
What is it now?
The smell of food from
other people's houses...
I can understand smelling something
like curry, but meat buns?
No, you can definitely smell it!
Haven't you ever run into someone
on the train who got takeout?
It's that smell! That guilty smell.
"Oh, yeah! Chinatown!"
What's with the time lag?
If you wait too long,
I can't remember what I was talking about.
I'm sorry.
It was funny, but I wasn't sure
I should interrupt, so I didn't.
Interrupt! Interrupt!
Taking these time-delayed jabs
feels kinda embarrassing.
"That guilty smell."
You're laughing at that now?
Where did you go in your free time
on the class trip?
Um, I went to a comedy show,
took photos in front of the signs...
visited the electronics district...
Really? Most of my class went to
Ultra Super Jumbo Land.
The photo you sent me of
the Inupii troop made me laugh.
It was fine buying those, but there's no
other opportunity to use them, you know?
Just a little while ago,
I was nervous because this isn't school,
but that anxiety has gradually lessened.
This situation, where there isn't anyone
else I know, actually feels comfortable.
I can't get the background in.
What if you turned it sideways?
It'd be nice if he felt the same way.
Hey, let's head over to that bridge, too.
Oh, wow!
It's pretty nice, right? This view.
What do I do?
Can't pay attention
to the scenery right now
I can't do this.
My heart's going to explode.
I can't look at his face.
Whoa, it's freezing!
It's cold near the ocean, huh?
Yamada-kun is behaving normally.
Am I the only one whose emotions
are racing around like idiots?
Huh?
That's...
Retreat!
Y-Yes, sir!
She's fast!
Wait! Nishi-san, you dropped something!
That scared me!
Things got weird at the very end.
Um, sorry my curfew is so early.
No, that's totally fine.
Can you breathe okay?
Oh, right. Earlier,
when you were running...
you dropped all kinds of stuff.
You didn't wear these today, right?
Do you always walk around with them?
Th-That's...
Since you have them,
you should put them on!
What?
It'll look cute!
Cute?
It's all fluffy.
Oh, the fluffiness is cute.
Huh? This is hard! Girls are amazing!
Oh. Sorry. It turned out weird.
But...
this way, you'll look me in the eye more.
Nishi-san, you hardly ever
look me in the eye, you know?
That's not a problem with my bangs.
It's a problem with my personality.
I'm sorry.
I'll make sure our gazes... meet-ry!
You say that, but your eyes are closed.
F-From now on...
From now on?
Let's hang out again! Just the two of us.
Yeah!
Retreat!
EXPLANATION
THE STATION WHERE THEY'RE MEETING
While Yamada and Nishi
were meeting at the station...
on that same day, about an hour earlier...
Wow! What a view!
A blue sky. An ocean view.
A popular sightseeing spot.
This really is...
super overtly a date.
What do I do?
My heart is pounding so hard!
On the class trip, there were times
it was just the two of us,
but we were basically always doing things
as a group, so there were people around.
GLOMP...
Is it okay if just for today
I indulge in being really close?
It's fine, right? I think it's fine!
NO REACTION...
Okay! Today, I just don't care!
CHINATOWN
After all...
Wow, those look yummy!
SNUG
we're a little ways away from
where we live, and it's just us two.
I want to try some fried xiao long bao.
SHARK FIN SHENG JIAN BAO
4 pc
yen
6 pc
tax inc.
SEAFOOD AND PORK COMBO
Yuusuke-han, whatcha fancy?
I have to enjoy this break
from everyday life!
The spring rolls look good.
Oh! Those would be good, too!
Right?
PERFECT VISION
Should we have lunch here, then?
Yeah.
FWIP
Huh? What's wrong—
Shh!
Don't speak. Don't turn around.
Move exactly as I tell you to.
Is that a threat?
Go into the restaurant
without making a sound.
Why?
I totally understand-ry.
EVERYDAY LIFE
Why?!
I was in uncommon
lovey-dovey girlfriend mode today!
Hang on! Did those two start dating?
Or is this that delicate period
before dating?
Either way, them being on a date
means it's all going super well, right?
HEH HEH HEH...
Hey, hey, Yamada!
I see. I see!
It'd make me happy if they
made an announcement later!
YAY
It's great that the skies
were clear today, right?
Yeah.
JUST RECENTLY
GLOMP
Wow!
That's so cool!
Cool?
Like, getting excited about a building.
I see.
Somehow...
a bayside night view feels like such
an adult sort of date, doesn't it?
Because you're using
so many English words?
But you're right.
I feel like I've grown a little.
Right?
The date is so date-like,
it's sort of embarrassing.
Yeah.
I wonder if Yamada
and Nissan will come here later.
If he tried sweet-talking her
in a fancy spot like this,
I'm sure she'd melt
and be totally bowled over.
Actually, what if they're
nearby right now?
I guess not, though.
So beautiful.
What?
The view.
Oh! Y-Yeah, it is.
Miyu-chan...
do you want to go over there?
Yuusuke-kun.
Wow! This is amazing!
Very urban.
I've always quietly thought about riding
a Ferris wheel with someone special.
Quietly?
No, I lie. Roaringly.
Roaringly?
THAT GOT
A LAUGH...
You see it a lot in live-action
movie adaptations of shojo manga,
so I've always wished I could do it.
Just live-action adaptations?
You have a point.
Just me and the person I love,
riding a Ferris wheel alone together.
Would it be all right if I sat over there?
What?
The situation I've always
longed to be in...
STARE...
They're really staring at us, aren't they?
I didn't know that Ferris wheel cars
were so easy to see into.
Let's take a photo for posterity!
That was so much fun!
The truth is, I wanted to be
a little more lovey-dovey...
but I don't want to be a sideshow, either.
The illumination display
was pretty, wasn't it?
We got our Christmas in early!
Yeah, that's true.
For Christmas,
it's that festive feeling leading up to
the day of that's the most fun, right?
I love this time of year!
Jingle bells! Jingle bells!
Do you want to do
something specific for Christmas?
Huh?
I'm not sure.
If it's the two of us...
then anything's fine.
Yuusuke-kun, what about you?
I feel the same.
As an aside...
right now... there's no one around.
WHOOM
STOPPED
A-A car!
Argh.
What's this?
Miyu! Yuusuke-kun!
My dad?!
Th-That was close!
You said you wouldn't need dinner,
so the two of us went out to eat!
It's been a while!
Yuusuke-kun, your house
is this way, right?
Yes, sir. Thank you.
THUMP
Wow, you rode the Ferris wheel?
The night view was gorgeous!
If only Ferris wheels spun faster,
they'd be so much fun!
That'd turn them into
something else, wouldn't it?
Suzuki, does that mean that
at last you've...
Exactly! A dream from my shojo manga
live-action movie mania has come true!
Nisshi, that pin is cute.
Oh, um... Thank you.
So...
was your outing fun?
What?
You went to Chinatown? I'm jealous!
Yeah. The meat buns were super good!
So, Yamada-kun went to Chinatown, too.
Who'd he go with?
No. I'm not asking that.
Wow. It's evening, but it kinda
already seems like night.
Your fingers are so cold.
Miyu-chan, why are you so warm?
PING
Yuusuke-han! Yuusuke-han! Look!
COCOA WITH CREAM
COZY
The "cozy and warm" lineup in
the vending machine has increased!
BOOM!
SATISFYING CORN POTAGE
CONSOMME SOUP
BEEF FLAVOR
Yay!
Doesn't it drive home that feeling
that the season has arrived?
SATISFYING CORN POTAGE
CORN POTAGE
You look forward to it every year?
Yup! And I will be a steady
patron again this year!
If you don't shake it a lot first,
you won't be able to go back,
so be careful.
That much?
Just like I can feel the seasons changing,
I want to be able to treasure
these small, positive changes, too.
Miyu or Miyu-chan...
If you don't know which to use,
I'm fine without.
SO IT DIDN'T SEEM
CASUAL AFTER ALL...
You'd like that better?
Yeah.
That version...
makes you more
self-conscious, Yuusuke-kun.
What kind of reason is that?
Miyu.
GLINT
Is that his "I'm not embarrassed" face?
Little by little, things change.
SQUIGGLE
There's just one more thing.
And I'm the one who did the nurturing.
HEH HEH...
Nurtured what?